anacapa.biz 2013-03-11

# The Anacapa Group

The Anacapa Group Privacy Notice

The Anacapa Group, Inc. ("The Anacapa Group") is committed to a policy that respects your privacy and protects the personal information you submit to us. The Anacapa Group understands that you care how your personal information is used. This privacy notice describes our policies regarding certain information collected on-line or off-line (whether transmitted manually or electronically). In the course of providing our services or products, we may otherwise collect certain anonymous information. If you agree to submit this type of information, you are consenting for us to use the information in accordance with the policies described in this notice. You should periodically visit this page as this notice may be modified from time to time to reflect changes in our policies.

Overall privacy statement

Because we gather certain types of anonymous information about our users, we want to help you understand:

* what information we collect

* how we use your information

* the choices you have with respect to your information

* the process by which your concerns with respect to our collection, use or disclosure of your information can be resolved

* our policy regarding information about children

1\. What personally identifiable information does The Anacapa Group collect?

The Anacapa Group doesn’t collect personally identifiable information at this time but may in the future. The Anacapa Group currently only collects anonymous information explained in point 2 below.

2\. What anonymous information does The Anacapa Group collect? Web-log data Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. Like many web sites, we use cookies to collect certain types of information when you visit our web site. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit The Anacapa Group.com, but certain personalized features will not be available to you if you disable or delete cookies created during your visits. You may elect not to allow cookies to be collected by selecting certain options on your browser.  The Anacapa Group also automatically receives and records information from our servers and from your browser, including your IP address, the time, and information about the page you requested.

We may use tracking technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

* keeping count of return visits to our site

* accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on our site and advertisement usage

* determining which features users like best

* displaying advertising targeted to your interests and usage of our site

Statistical Data

The Anacapa Group may collect certain statistical data that does not identify you. You will be prompted each time we ask for this information, and you will have the option to provide it or not. We aggregate this information and use it for the same types of purposes as we use web-log data.

3\. What about advertisements?

Advertisers on our web site are allowed to gather information using cookies and other tracking technologies as set forth above. Except as specifically set forth in this privacy notice, The Anacapa Group does not share your personally identifiable information with advertisers. Advertisers on The Anacapa Group.com cannot identify you personally unless you register with them or specifically provide such information. If you submit personally identifiable information directly to one of our advertisers, the use, disclosure and protection of your information will be according to that advertiser's privacy policy. You should read each advertiser's privacy notice prior to submitting any personally identifiable information to that advertiser.

4\. How will you know if the privacy policy changes?

Our business changes over time and our privacy practices may be modified as our business changes. Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first in this notice of our Privacy Policy, so you should check our site frequently to watch for changes. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy notice. If we are going to be using the information collected from users in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify affected users of the change via email.

5\. What if you have a question or concern about your our privacy policy?

If you have a question or concern about the collection, use, or access to your information, about this privacy notice, or about any other aspects of The Anacapa Group.com, please contact us through our contact form. Provide us with a thorough description of your question or concern and we will attempt to answer or resolve it. If our customer service department does not satisfy your concern, we will escalate your concern to appropriate management within The Anacapa Group.

In the unlikely event that we cannot adequately address your concern, you and The Anacapa Group will attempt in good faith to resolve any bona fide dispute relating in any way to our collection, use, or handling of your personal information by confidential mediation under the CPR Mediation Procedure. Mediation of the dispute will be conducted on an agreed date by a single, agreed upon, independent mediator in Dublin, Ireland, or another agreed location. Any bona fide dispute not resolved within a reasonable period of time by discussion or mediation will be finally resolved by confidential arbitration in accordance with the CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution Rules for Non-Administered Arbitration by a sole arbitrator in Dublin, Ireland or another agreed location. For more information about dispute resolution, see the procedures set forth in our Terms of Service.

6\. Privacy of children

The Anacapa Group is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.

7\. Safe Harbor

The Anacapa Group is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor web site [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor]. If you would like to contact The Anacapa Group directly about the Safe Harbor program, please contact us through our contact form.

Updated October 2010
